We are about to go thicky thicky for the record with Kid and Play.
I'ma start with Play.
You have said that you was a hard rock growing up.
No, no, I wasn't a hard rock.
I was an idiot, but yeah.
Dang, that's better than a hard rock.
All right, all right.
What's a song that you feel describes that era of your life?
That's The Way of the World, Earth, Wind & Fire.
Oh, Earth, Wind & Fire.
I mean, they describe the journey of a child and the thing, you know, unknowing, not knowing your value, all of that, Pearl, all of that.
All right, Kid, what is a song that speaks to your love life?
Bad luck!
That's what you got.
Why bad luck?
Bad luck.
You don't want LL Cool J's or Need Love?
You don't want that?
No, how about Better Have My Money?
Oh, my gosh.
So I'm taking from this, you're single.
I mean, I'm divorced, but I found love after that.
Oh, that's beautiful.
Yeah, yeah.
I got an ex-wife, two baby mamas, and a girlfriend.
Okay, so you are a rapper.
Okay.
Right.
People don't understand.
In order to get in the rapper's union back in the day, you had to have at least two baby mamas.
It's what they call a two baby mama minimum.
Okay.
All right, that was part of the bylaws.
Yeah, I'm a union man.
I follow the rules.
We are, we are, we are.